mymove.com 2019-01-15

# Privacy Policy | MYMOVE

Effective as of November 5, 2018

Welcome to MYMOVE.com (the various websites, applications, widgets, email notifications and other mediums, or portions of such mediums, through which you may have accessed MYMOVE.com and/or this Privacy Policy, collectively, the “Site”), and thank you for taking the time to read these terms, conditions, and provisions regarding our information collection, retention, use and disclosure practices (our “Privacy Policy”).

The Site is owned and operated by MYMOVE, LLC (the “Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our”), a Red Ventures company. We are committed to respecting the privacy of visitors to our Site. This Privacy Policy provides you with notice of how we currently collect, transfer, store, disclose and use information gathered from or provided by you through or in connection with the Site. Your continued access or use of the Site constitutes your consent to our collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information (including personal information) as described in this Privacy Policy from time to time.

## **The following topics are presented in this Privacy Policy:**

  1. [**Collecting and Using Personal Information from Website Visitors:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#1collectingandusingpersonalinformation)
  2. [**Methods of Information Collection:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#2methodsofinformationcollection)
  3. [**Affiliate Marketing Programs and Third-Party Cookies:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#3affiliatemarketingprogramsandthirdpartycookies)
  4. [**Using and Sharing Personal Information:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#4usingandsharingpersonalinformation)
  5. [**Protecting Personal Information:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#5protectingpersonalinformation)
  6. [**Transferring Personal Information To Other Countries**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#6transferringpersonalinformationtoothercountries)
  7. [**Blogs and Public Forums**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#7blogsandpublicforums)
  8. [**Visiting Non-Company Websites:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#8visitingnoncompanywebsites)
  9. [**Children’s Information**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#9childrensinformation)
  10. [**Your Choices:**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#10yourchoices)
  11. [**Our Right to Change this Privacy Policy**](https://mymove.com/privacy-policy/#11ourrighttochangethisprivacypolicy)

## 1.  **Collecting and Using Personal Information**

_Information You Provide Voluntarily_

Certain features of the Site are only available to our registered users, and to access those areas of the Site you may be required to go through a registration and log-in process, after which you may log into the Site or certain features or areas thereof using your username and email password. You may also be required to provide personal and/or demographic information as part of the registration or log-in process. Personal information is information that can be used to identify you individually, and may include information like your name, postal address, telephone number, fax number, e-mail address, credit card number, subscriber name or screen name, and password used to access the Site.

We may also collect information provided by visitors in registration forms, surveys, sweepstakes, games or other contest entries, emails, texts, and other submissions or electronic messaging to us. If you choose to participate in any such activities, or if you choose to otherwise access or use any part of the Site or any of the services provided on or through the Site, we may receive or request certain personal information from you, including information like your contact information, date of birth, geolocation, past, present or future postal address, moving date and related information, information about other people like your friends and family members, information about your hobbies and interests, and information about past, present or future activities or events undertaken by you, and/or other people like your friends or family members.

Participation in all Site services and activities is completely voluntary, and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

_Information We Collect Automatically_

We also collect and track automatically (1) the home server domain names, IP addresses, type of client device, and type of web browser of visitors to our Site, and (2) aggregate and specific information on what pages visitors access. We may combine your personal information with other information collected from and about you on the Site, from third parties, or from other online and offline sources.

_Cross-Device Data Linking_

We may also receive, use, or transfer data collected from one device to other devices that may be linked to or associated (i.e., through a common IP address) with the same user of the device where data was collected. We use the term “devices” to refer collectively to computers and mobile devices, as well as Internet browsers and other applications on your devices that interact with the Internet.

## 2.  **Methods of Information Collection**

The information collection described above may use several automatic data collection tools and techniques, including cookies, clickstream, and web beacons.

  * Cookies and Tracking Technologies: Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Company and our partners and affiliates, or by analytics applications. These technologies may be used in analyzing trends, administering the Site, tracking users’ movements around the Site and other websites, and gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies to remember users’ settings (e.g., language preference) and customize their experiences, as well as for user authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of the Site may be limited.
  * Log Files: Like many websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you, in part to improve Site functionality and the services we make available to you.
  * Behavioral Advertising: If you would like to generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third-party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising, please visit the opt-out pages on the NAI website and the DAA website or click the following: NAI’s opt-out tool: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>DAA’s opt out tool: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>
  * Local Storage: We use Local Storage (LS) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LS such as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.
  * Single Sign-On: You may log in to the Site using sign-on services such as Google Sign-In, Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us to pre-populate our registration form, such as your name and email address. These sign-on services may also give you the option to post information about your activities on this Site to your profile page for sharing with others in your network.
  * Social Media Widgets: Our Site may include social media features such as the Facebook Like button and/or other features that allow you to share content or experiences on our Site or interact with our Site using the feature. These features may collect your IP address and the page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the social media feature to function properly. These social media features are hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature.
  * Data Analytics: We use certain web analytics services, including third-party services such as Google Analytics, to help us understand and analyze how visitors use the Site. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies on both an individual and aggregated basis. These analytics services, including third-party services such as Google Analytics, also use this information to place advertisements for our products on other websites that you visit after your use of the Site. These advertisements may be based on the pages you visited during your use of the Site. For further information about how Google may use data it collects through the Site you may visit <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>. You also may choose to install the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on to opt out of Google Analytics data collection, by visiting <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>. Your web browser may have settings that allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites or use online services. Like many websites, this Site is not designed to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. To learn more about “Do Not Track” signals, you may wish to visit <http://www.allaboutdnt.com/>.

## 3.  **Affiliate Marketing Programs and Third-Party Cookies**

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. MYMOVE may also participate in other third-party affiliate marketing programs that allow MYMOVE to earn commissions when you click on (and/or make purchases using) links to companies, brands, products, and/or services on the MYMOVE site. To help keep track of the commissions we earn, the companies who provide these programs may place third-party cookies on your computer or mobile device. By clicking on links on MYMOVE, you consent to placement and use of cookies as described in, and the other terms of, the following privacy policies:

  * Amazon: [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)
  * Pepperjam: <https://www.pepperjam.com/legal>
  * Impact Radius: <https://impact.com/privacy-policy/>
  * ShareASale: [shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf](http://www.shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf)

## 4.  **Using and Sharing Personal Information**

We may use information we collect from and about you for various purposes, including:

  * To maintain an account in your name from which you can initiate and receive communications with us;
  * To respond to your inquiries, and to send you information you have requested and additional information about us, our services, and third-party advertisers;
  * To fulfill orders, provide service, and communicate with customers;
  * To research, test and develop new products, services, features, promotions, and functionality;
  * To make your use of the Site more convenient;
  * To provide you and other users with customized website content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Site, on other sites, or via email or other electronic communication across multiple devices;
  * To customize ads and to manage and facilitate messaging on third party sites, including but not limited to Facebook, Google, and Twitter;
  * To contact you, including with regard to your account and for other non-marketing or administrative purposes;
  * To review the traffic to and usage and operations of our Site and improve our content, products, and services;
  * To address problems with the Site or our business;
  * To promote the Site;
  * To manage our telecommunications networks;
  * To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business; and
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection.

We may disclose information (including personal information) we collect from and about you as follows: (1) to any service provider that operates our Site and their affiliated companies; (2) to other service providers if the disclosure will enable or assist them to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us; (3) as necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement or regulatory agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (5) in our judgment, to comply with applicable law, or to protect the interests or safety of other persons or property, including Company, its affiliates, and other users or advertisers using the Site; (6) to third parties offering products or services on the Site; (7) to other select third parties that we believe may have offers of interest to you; (8) to promote the Site and our business to third parties; (9) as described to you at the point of collection; and (10) for general business purposes within the Company’s family of businesses, including its parent company, affiliates and subsidiaries. We may also share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties. If you opt in to participate in any referral service we may offer, we use the information you submit to determine which of our participating professional(s) may be able to serve your needs. We may then disclose your information, which may include personal information, contained on our sign-up form to certain professional(s), who may then contact you via telephone, email, or other electronic communication regarding the service. In any or all cases of such disclosure(s) to a third party described in this Privacy Policy, we may be compensated for such disclosure(s), and your information will become subject to the information collection, retention, use and disclosure practices of the third party, and the third party will not be restricted by this Privacy Policy with respect to its use and further sharing of your information. We may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to obtain the transferee’s agreement to use personal information provided through this Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. California Privacy Rights: California law permits customers in California to request certain details about how their personal information is shared with third parties and, in some cases, affiliates, if the personal information is shared for those third parties’ and affiliates’ own direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you may request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us in writing at 1101 Red Ventures Drive, Fort Mill, SC 29707, Attn: Privacy Officer, or [privacy@redventures.com](mailto:privacy@redventures.com). To make a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident, and provide your current California address to which we will send our response. Your inquiry must specify “California Privacy Rights Request” in the subject line of the email or the first line of the letter, and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year.

## 5.  **Protecting Personal Information**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain reasonable generally-accepted administrative, technical and physical measures to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, no method of Internet transmission or electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you choose to create an account on our Site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account password and for any activity that occurs under your account. We are not liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to protect your password or account information. Please notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account promptly after becoming aware of such unauthorized use by emailing [privacy@redventures.com](mailto:privacy@redventures.com).

## 6.  **Transferring Personal Information to Other Countries**

The country in which you are doing business with us or where the Site you are visiting is located/hosted may have specific requirements concerning personal information. Where permitted by local laws and regulatory requirements, we may transfer personal information we collect on our Site to other countries where we, and our service providers, do business, but we will do so only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

## 7.  **Blogs and Public Forums**

Our Site may offer publicly available blogs, bulletin boards, chat rooms, ratings or reviews, or other community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected and used by others who access them. We encourage you to be cautious when submitting personal information in these public areas. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacy@mymove.com](mailto:helpdesk@mymove.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information. In that event, we will provide appropriate notice to you.

## 8.  **Visiting Non-Company Websites**

Our Site may contain links to other websites, which may have privacy policies and/or information collection, retention, use and disclosure practices that differ from our own. Company is not responsible for the practices (including the information collection, retention, use and disclosure practices) or content of websites other than the Site. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies and information collection, retention, use and disclosure practices. We encourage you to be aware of the privacy policies and information collection, retention, use and disclosure practices of each website with which you may interact.

## 9.  **Children’s Information**

This Site is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 should provide information to our Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18, do not use, register for, provide information to, or use any of the interactive or public features of this Site, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may have. If we learn that we have received information directly from a child who is under the age of 18, we will delete the information as required by applicable law. California residents under the age of 18 who have registered to use the Site, and who have posted content or information on the Site, can request that such information be removed from the Site by contacting us at [privacy@mymove.com](mailto:helpdesk@mymove.com) or by sending a letter to 1101 Red Ventures Drive, Fort Mill, SC 29707, Attn: Privacy Officer, stating that they personally posted such content or information and detailing where the content or information is posted. We will make reasonable good faith efforts to remove the post from prospective public view or anonymize it so the minor cannot be individually identified. However, this removal process cannot ensure complete or comprehensive deletion from the Internet.

## 10.  **Your Choices**

If you wish to update or remove your personal information, opt out from receiving, or opt in to receive, marketing communications from us please do so by indicating your preferences by contacting us at 1101 Red Ventures Drive, Fort Mill, SC 29707, Attn: Privacy Policy Manager, or [privacy@mymove.com](mailto:helpdesk@mymove.com). If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the same mailing or email address. Where required by law, you may request access to your personal information that we maintain. As permitted by law, we may charge a reasonable fee for providing access to personal information, but we do not charge for lodging a request for access. We may retain your information indefinitely in accordance with applicable law. You may elect to terminate your MYMOVE account at any time by sending an email to us at [privacy@mymove.com](mailto:helpdesk@mymove.com). If you do, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete your personal information on our servers, although some data that cannot be removed in a commercially reasonable manner may remain in the MYMOVE secure database. Additionally, your data that was previously archived may be stored in our offline backups. However, we will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## 11.  **Our Right to Change this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. If we do so, we may let you know by posting the modified Policy on this Site or through other communications. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to this Privacy Policy. It is important that you review the Privacy Policy whenever modified because your continued use of the Site will indicate your acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy, then you may not use the Site anymore. We will indicate the Privacy Policy’s effective date on the first page.
